A Guide to the Lester M. Salamon Papers FA1868
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Books, 1964-2020; 3; 8.47 Cubic Feet (10 containers)
  - Subsidiarity Governance: Theoretical and Empirical Models, Alessandro Colombo, 2012 (Box 47)
  - Społeczeństwo Obywatelskie: badania, praktyka, polityka: zeszyty naukowe Zakładu Rozwoju Społeczeństwa Obywatelskiego, 2016 (Box 47)
  - Human Capital and American's Future: An Economic Strategy for the 90s, David W. Hornbeck and Lester M. Salamon, 1991 (Box 47)
    Two copies.
  - For Lester M. Salamon with Appreciation and Thanks from His Hungarian Friends, undated (Box 47)
    Two copies: one bound blue volume and one spiral notebook.
  - The Nonprofit Sector in Hungary, Eva Kuti, 1996 (Box 47)
  - The Emerging Nonprofit Sector: An Overview, Lester M. Salamon and Helmut K. Anheier, 1996 (Box 47)
    Three copies: 2 paperback, one hardcover.
  - The Nonprofit Sector in Japan, Tadashi Yamamoto, 1998 (Box 47)
  - The Nonprofit Sector in Italy, Gian Paolo Barbetta, 1997 (Box 47)
  - Defining the Nonprofit Sector: A Cross-National Analysis, Lester M. Salamon and Helmut K. Anheier, 1997 (Box 47)
  - The Regan Presidency and the Governing America, Lester M. Salamon and Michael S. Lund, 1985 (Box 47)
  - Federal Reorganization: What Have We Learned?, Peter Szanton, 1981 (Box 47)
  - The Illusion of Presidential Government, Hugh Helco and Lester M. Salamon, 1981 (Box 47)
  - Holding the Center: America's Nonprofit Sector at a Crossroads, Lester M. Salamon, 1997 (Box 47)
  - il Progetto: il Lavoro Non Profit in Difesa del Welfare e dei Meno Fortunati, 1997 (Box 47)
  - The Time Dimension in Policy Evaluation: The Case of the New Deal Land-Reform Experiments, Lester M. Salamon, 1979 (Box 47)
  - The Third Sector Project Helping to Build A Nonprofit Sector in Central and Eastern Europe: Training Manual, Nicole Etchart-Mendoza and Lester M. Salamon, 1992 (Box 47)
  - Les Nouvelle Soliarites: Actes des Assisses Internationales de Janvier, 1989 (Box 48)
  - The Practice of Comparative Politics, Paul G. Lewis, David C. Potter, and Francis G. Castles, 1978 (Box 48)
  - The Jossey-Bass Handbook of Nonprofit Leadership and Management, Second Edition, Robert D. Herman and Associates, 2005 (Box 48)
    Contains "The Changing Context of American Nonprofit Management" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Globalization, Philanthropy, and Civil Society: Toward a New Political Culture in the Twenty-First Century, Soma Hewa and Darwin H. Stapleton, 2005 (Box 48)
  - The Third Sector: Sustainable Development, Evelyn Berg Ioscpe, 1997 (Box 48)
  - The Emerging Sector: An Overview, Lester M. Salamon and Helmut K. Anheier, 1994 (Box 48)
  - The Black Rural Landowner - Endangered Species: Social, Political, and Economic Implications, Leo McGee and Robert Boone, 1979 (Box 48)
  - Administration and Society, Volume 12, Number 4, 1981 February (Box 48)
  - The Resilient Sector Revisited: The New Challenge to Nonprofit American, Lester M. Salamon, 2015 (Box 48)
  - Rethinking Corporate Social Engagement: Lessons from Latin America, Lester M. Salamon, 2010 (Box 48)
  - Measuring Research and Development Expenditures in the U.S. Nonprofit Sector: Conceptual and Design Issues, Summary of a Workshop, National Research Council, 2014 (Box 48)
  - The Resilient Sector: The State of Nonprofit America, Lester M. Salamon, 2003 (Box 48)
  - Homeless Children and Youth: A New American Dilemma, Julee H. Kryder-Coe, Lester M. Salamon, and Janice M. Molnar, 1991 (Box 48)
  - The Money Committees: A Study of the House Banking and Currency Committee and the Senate Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs Committee, Ralph Nader Congess Project, Lester M. Salamon, 1975 (Box 48)
  - O Quinto Poder – Consciência Social de uma Nação, Lillian Dreyer, Maria Elenda Pereira Johannpeter, 2008 (Box 48)
  - Competition in the U.S. Energy Industry: A Report to the Energy Policy Project of the Ford Foundation, Thomas D. Duchesneau, 1975 (Box 48)
  - Growing Metropolis: Aspects of Development in Nashville, James F. Blumstein and Benjamin Walter, 1975 (Box 48)
  - Public Policy, Volume 27, Number 2, 1979 Spring (Box 48)
    Contains "The Time Dimension in Policy Evaluation: The Case of the New Deal Land-Reform Experiments, Lester M. Salamon
  - Public Policy Making in a Federal System, Charles O. Jones and Robert D. Thomas, 1976 (Box 48)
  - Transatlantic Perspectives on Liberalization and Democratic Governance, Eberhard Bohne, Charles F. Bonser, and Kenneth M. Spencer, 2004 (Box 49)
  - America's Nonprofit Sector: A Primer, Lester M. Salamon, 2012 (Box 49)
  - Welfare: The Elusive Consensus - Where We Are, How We Got Here, and What's Ahead, A Report from the Welfare Policy Project of the Ford Foundation and Duke University, Lester M. Salamon, 1978 (Box 49)
  - La Societa' Generosa, Vello Pier Mario, Reolon Martina, Lester M. Salamon, 2014 (Box 49)
  - Partners in Public Service: Government-Nonprofit Relations in the Modern Welfare State, Lester M. Salamon, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Social Service Review, Volume 67, Number 1, 1993 March (Box 49)
    Contains "The Marketization of Welfare: Changing Nonprofit and For-Profit Roles in the American Welfare State" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Challenges for a Global Welfare System, Peter Herrmann, 1998 (Box 49)
    Contains "The Nonprofit Sector: A New Global Force" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - On the front lines of NPOs: American civil society at a crossroads, 1999 (Box 49)
  - America's Nonprofit Sector, Lester M. Salamon, 1994 (Box 49)
  - Fordham Urban Law Journal, Tenth Annual Symposium on Contemporary Urban Challenges, Redefining the Public Sector: Accountability and Democracy in the Era of Privatization, 2001 June (Box 49)
    Contains "The Changing Shape of Government" panel discussion, and "The New Governance and the Tools of Public Action: An Introduction" article by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Non Dan, Volume 7, Number 3, 1971 November-December (Box 49)
    Contains "Comparative History and the Theory of Modernization" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - A harmadik szektor. Tanulmányok, 1991 (Box 49)
  - Szektor születik: A NONPROFIT SZEKTOR NEMZETKÖZI ÖSSZEHASONLÍTÁSBAN, Lester M. Salamon and Helmut K. Anheier, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Protest, Politics, and Modernization in the American South: Mississippi as a "Developing Society," Lester Milton Salamon, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Institute for Policy Studies with a Global Reach, Johns Hopkins University, undated (Box 50, Folder 385)
  - The Journal of Intergroup Relations, Volume 14, Number 3, 1986 Fall (Box 50, Folder 386)
    Contains "Government and the Voluntary Sector in an Era of Retrenchment: The American Experience" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Leadership and Modernization: The Emerging Black Political Elite in the American South, Lester M. Salamon, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 387)
  - The Operating Budget As A Steering Device, Gary L. Wamsley and Lester M. Salamon, undated (Box 50, Folder 388)
  - Government and the Voluntary Sector In An Era of Retrenchment: The American Experience, Lester M. Salamon, undated (Box 50, Folder 389)
  - Rethinking Public Management: Third-Party Government and the Changing Forms of Government Action, Lester M. Salamon, 1981 Summer (Box 50, Folder 390)
  - The Rise of the Nonprofit Sector, Foreign Affairs, Volume 73, Number 4, Lester M. Salamon, 1994 July-August (Box 50, Folder 391)
  - Proposal: A Citizen's Budget, Political Analysis, Volume 2, Number 4, Lester M. Salamon, 1976 Fall (Box 50, Folder 392)
  - Social Origins of Civil Society: Explaining the Nonprofit Sector Cross-Nationally, Voluntas, Volume 9, Number 3, Lester M. Salamon, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 393)
  - The Voluntary Sector and the Future of the Welfare State, Nonprofit and Voluntary Sector Quarterly, Volume 17, Number 1, Lester M. Salamon, 1989 Spring (Box 50, Folder 394)
  - The Marketization of Welfare: Changing Nonprofit and For-Profit Roles in the American Welfare State, Social Service Review, Volume 67, Number 1, Lester M. Salamon, 1993 March (Box 50, Folder 395)
  - Pittsburg Nonprofit Organizations: The Challenge of Retrenchment, Lester M. Salamon, David M. Altschuler, and Carol J. De Vita, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 396)
  - Privatization: The Challenge to Public Management, National Academy of Public Administration (NAPA) Report, 1989 March (Box 50, Folder 397)
  - Public Administration Review, Number 4, 1977 July-August (Box 50, Folder 398)
    Contains "Urban Politics, Urban Policy, Case Studies, and Political Theory" book review by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Economia del Sector No Lucrativo, Colegio de Madrid, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 399)
  - Maryland and the New World Economy: Challenges and Opportunities, Institute for Policy Studies, Lester M. Salamon, 1991 November (Box 50, Folder 400)
  - Der Dritte Sektor: Aktuelle internationale trends, Johns Hopkins University Comparative Nonprofit Sector Project, Lester M. Salamon and Helmut K. Anheier, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 401)
  - Globalizarea Sectorului Nonprofit: O Revizuire, Lester M. Salamon and Helmut K. Anheier, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 402)
  - White Papers On: Securing America's Future: Achieving U.S. Technology Independence and Job Growth - Responding to the Challenge, Lester M. Salamon, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 403)
  - The Third Route: Government-Nonprofit Collaboration in Germany and the U.S., Lester M. Salamon and Helmut K. Anheier, 1996 June (Box 50, Folder 404)
  - Plenary Highlights from the 1995 Independent Sector Annual Meeting, Boston, Massachusetts (Box 50, Folder 405)
    Contains "Winds of Change - Implications for the Sector" plenary session by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Poverty Amidst Plenty: The Two Faces of Anne Arundel County: A Guide to Action, 2005 June (Box 50, Folder 406)
  - Grassroots Development, Journal of the Inter-American Foundation, Volume 29, Number 1, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 407)
  - VEP News, Voter Education Project, Volume 5, Number 2, 1971 July-September (Box 50, Folder 408)
  - Land and Minority Enterprise: The Crisis and the Opportunity, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 409)
  - The Nonprofit Quarterly: Leadership Transitions: Critical Thresholds, 2002 Winter (Box 51, Folder 410)
    Contains "The Resilient Sector: The State of Nonprofit America" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Serving Community Needs: The Nonprofit Sector in an Era of Government Retrenchment, The Nonprofit Sector Project, Progress Report 2, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 411)
  - Satellite Account on Non-Profit and Related Institutions and Volunteer Work, 2018 (Box 51, Folder 412)
  - Bulleti Balear d'Economia, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 413)
    Contains "The New Economy" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Parrots and Pragmatists: Soviet Leadership Dispute in the Development of Policy Towards the Machine and Tractor Stations, Lester M. Salamon, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 414)
  - Urban Politics, Urban Policy, Case Studies and Political Theory, Lester M. Salamon, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 415)
  - Economic Power and Political Influence: Impact of Industry Structure on Public Policy, Lester M. Salamon and John J. Siegfried, undated (Box 51, Folder 416)
  - Public Land and Minority Enterprise: A New Policy Option, Research Report Number 4, Duke-OMBE Project, Lester M. Salamon and David Perry, 1975 March (Box 51, Folder 417)
  - The Time Dimension in Policy Evaluation: The Case of the New Deal Land Reform Experiments, Lester M. Salamon, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 418)
  - The Federal Budget and the Nonprofit Sector, Lester M. Salamon and Alan J. Abramson, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 419)
  - Navigating the Future: Making Headway on Sustainability for Social Accountability Organizations, GPSA Working Paper Series, Lester M. Salamon, Stephanie Geller, S. Woichiech Sokolowski, 2014 December (Box 51, Folder 420)
  - Foundation News, Washington, D.C. - Long on Power, Short on Charity, 1985 March-April (Box 51, Folder 421)
  - Federalism: Making the System Work, Center for National Policy, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 422)
  - Forum for Applied Research and Public Policy, Volume 12, Number 4, 1997 Winter (Box 52, Folder 423)
    Contains "Will Federal Budget Cuts Increase Burden of Charities?" by Alan Abramson and Lester Salamon.
  - Durham Urban Observatory Report: The Substandard Rental Housing Market in Durham Toward An Inner-City Housing Policy, Lester M. Salamon, 1976 July (Box 52, Folder 424)
  - The Federal Government and the Nonprofit Sector: Implications of the Reagan Budget Proposals, Lester M. Salamon and Alan J. Abramson, 1981 May (Box 52, Folder 425)
  - Nonprofits: The Results Are Coming In, Lester M. Salamon, 1981 July-August (Box 52, Folder 426)
  - The Federal Government and the Nonprofit Sector: The Impact of the 1981 Tax Act on Individual Charitable Giving, A Study for Independent Sector, Charles T. Clotfelter and Lester M. Salamon, 1981 August (Box 52, Folder 427)
  - The Jackson Nonprofit Sector in a Time of Government Retrenchment, Lester M. Salamon, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 428)
  - The Canadian Nonprofit and Voluntary Sector in Comparative Perspective, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 429)
  - Satellite Accounts of Nonprofit Institutions and Volunteering, 2004 September (Box 52, Folder 430)
  - Government Spending and the Nonprofit Sector in Two Arizona Communities: Phoenix/Maricopa County and Pinal County, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 431)
  - The Emerging Sector: A Statistical Supplement, Lester M. Salamon, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 432)
  - Pennsylvania Nonprofit EMployment, Lester M. Salamon, Stephanie Lessans Geller, and S. Wojciech Sokolowski, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 433)
  - Defining the Nonprofit Sector: Egypt, Amani Kandil, 1993 May (Box 52, Folder 434)
  - September 11: The Philanthropic Response, The Foundation Center, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 435)
  - Global Civil Society: An Overview, Lester M. Salamon, S. Wojciech Sokolowski, and Regina List, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 436)
  - Annals of Public and Comparative Economics, Volume 82, Number 3, 2011 September (Box 53, Folder 437)
    Contains "Measuring the Economic Value of Volunteer Work Globally: Concepts, Estimates, and a Roadmap to the Future" by Lester M. Salamon, S. Wojciech Sokolowski, and Meagan A. Haddock.
  - Johns Hopkins Institute for Policy Studies, Projects and Programs, 2007-2008 (Box 53, Folder 438)
  - Fear, Apathy, and Discrimination: A Test of Three Explanations of Political Participation, Lester M. Salamon and Stephen Van Evera, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 439)
  - Comment: A Re-evaluation of Black Voting in Mississippi (Sam Kernell) and Fear Revisited: Rejoinder to "Comment" by Sam Kernell (Lester M. Salamon and Stephen Van Evera), 1973 (Box 53, Folder 440)
  - Bell Atlantic Quarterly, Volume 1, Number 1, 1984 Autumn (Box 53, Folder 441)
    Contains "The Invisible Partnership: Government and the Nonprofit Sector" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - News South: A Quarterly Review of Southern Affairs, Volume 27, Number 1, 1972 Winter (Box 53, Folder 442)
    Contains "Mississippi Post-Mortem: The 1971 Elections" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Journal of Voluntary Action Research, Volume 16, Numbers 1 and 2, 1987 January-June (Box 53, Folder 443)
    Contains "Of Market Failure, Voluntary Failure, and Third-Party Government: Toward A Theory of Government-Nonprofit Relations in the Modern Welfare State" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - The World Financial Review: A Win-Win Route Out of the Greek Debt Crisis, Lester M. Salamon, 2015 May-June (Box 53, Folder 444)
  - Maryland Nonprofits: Celebrating 25 Years, undated (Box 53, Folder 445)
    Lester M. Salamon, Founders Award.
  - Reorganization Study of Local Development Assistance Programs: Staff Analysis, President's Reorganization Project, 1978 December (Box 53, Folder 446)
  - Atlantide: Un Mondo Che Fa Parlare Altri Mondi: Alla ricerca del nuovo leader, 2007 September (Box 53, Folder 447)
    Contains: "Nuova governance e attivita pubblica" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Foreign Policy: Business Goes to War, 2002 May-June (Box 53, Folder 448)
    Contains "Social Engagement" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Estudio Sobre el Sector sin Fines de Lucro en Argentina, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 449)
  - Atlantide: Un Mondo Che Fa Parlare Altri Mondi: La ricchezza delle nazioni, 2008 (Box 53, Folder 450)
    Contains "Verso una societa a tre settori" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Foundation News: The Philanthropy of Organized Religion, First-Ever Survey on its Scope, Size, 1984 September-October (Box 53, Folder 451)
  - Kurázci: A Civil Társadalom Lapja, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 452)
  - The Global Association Revolution: The Rise of the Third Sector on the World Scene, Lester M. Salamon, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 453)
  - Economia Pubblica: mensile di studi e d'informazione a cura del Ciriec, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 454)
    Contains "Quale futuro per il Welfare State" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Annals of Public and Cooperative Economics, Volume 81, Number 2, 2010 June (Box 54, Folder 455)
    Contains "Putting the Civil Society Sector on the Economic Map of the World" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Nonprofit and Voluntary Sector Quarterly, Volume 18, Number 1, 1989 Spring (Box 54, Folder 456)
    Contains "The Voluntary Sector and the Future of the Welfare State" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Nonprofit and Voluntary Sector Quarterly, Volume 49, Number 5, 2020 October (Box 54, Folder 457)
    Contains "Subnational Variations in Civil Society Development: The Suprising Case" by Lester M. Salamon, Yulia Skokova, and Irina Krasnopolskaya.
  - Defining the Nonprofit Sector: India, Siddhartha Sen, 1993 May (Box 54, Folder 458)
  - Defining the Nonprofit Sector: Germany, Helmut K. Anheier and Wolfgang Seibel, 1993 May (Box 54, Folder 459)
  - Defining the Nonprofit Sector: Italy, Gian Paolo Barbetta, 1993 May (Box 54, Folder 460)
  - Defining the Nonprofit Sector: Hungary, Eva Kuti, 1993 May (Box 54, Folder 461)
  - Nuevo Estudio del Sector Emergente: Resumen, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 462)
  - The Emerging Sector Revisited: A Summary, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 463)
  - Descubriendo el sector sin fines de lucro en Argentina: su estructura y su importancia economia, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 464)
  - The New Zealand Non-Profit Sector in Comparative Perspective, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 465)
  - The Influence of the Legal Environment on the Development of the Nonprofit Sector, Lester M. Salamon and Stefan Toepler, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 466)
  - Economic Development and Minority Enterprise: The Sea Islands of South Carolina, Dennis Warner and Lester M. Salamon, undated (Box 54, Folder 467)
  - The Nonprofit Sector: A Research Handbook, Walter W. Powell, 1987 (Box 55)
    Contains "Partners in Public Service: The Scope and Theory of Government Nonprofit Relations" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - The Nonprofit Sector: A Research Handbook, Second Edition, Walter W. Powell and Richard Steinberg, 2006 (Box 55)
    Contains "The Nonprofit Sector in Comparative Perspective" by Helmut K. Anheier and Lester M. Salamon.
  - Private Action and the Public Good, Walter W. Powell and Elisabeth S. Clemens, 1998 (Box 55)
    Contains "The Third Route: Government-Nonprofit Collaboration in Germany and the United States" by Lester M. Salamon and Helmut K. Anheier.
  - The Nonprofit Sector in France, Edith Archambault, 1997 (Box 55)
  - The Nonprofit Sector in Sweden, Tommy Lundström and Filip Wijkström, 1997 (Box 55)
  - Global Civil Society: Dimensions of the Nonprofit Sector, 1999 (Box 55)
  - Capacity for Change? The Nonprofit World in the Age of Devolution, 1996 (Box 55)
    Contains "The Federal Budget and the Nonprofit Sector" by Lester M. Salamon.
  - Government and the Third Sector: Emerging Relationships in Welfare States, Gidron, Kramer, Salamon, 1992 (Box 55)
  - Care and Community in Modern Society: Passing on the Tradition of Service to Future Generations, 1995 (Box 55)
    Contains "Caring Sector or Caring Society: Discovering the Nonprofit Sector Cross-Nationally" by Lester M. Salamon and Helmut K. Anheier.
  - Tools of Government: A Guide to the New Governance, Lester M. Salamon, 2002 (Box 55)
  - Sociedad en accion: construyendo Chile desde las organizaciones de la sociedad civil, 2017 (Box 55)
  - America's Nonprofit Sector: A Primer, Second Edition, Lester M. Salamon, 1999 (Box 55)
- Reference Material, 1971-1992; 4; 0.76 Cubic Feet (2 containers)
  This series contains copies of primary and secondary sources not authored by Salamon that were likely used as reference material for his writings.
  - Purchase of Social Service: Study of the Experience of the Three States in Purchase of Service by Contract Under the Provisions of the 1967 Amendments to the Social Security Act, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 483)
  - Purchase of Service Contracting, Peter M. Kettner and Lawrence L. Martin, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 484)
  - Purchase of Service Contracting and the Declining Influence of Social Work, Peter M. Kettner and Lawrence L. Martin, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 485)
  - Factors Affecting Competition in State Contracting for Human Services, Peter M. Kettner and Lawrence L. Martin, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 486)
  - State Services for Children: An Exploration of Who Benefits, Who Governs, Michael Kirst, et al, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 487)
  - Nonprofit Organizations, Government, and the Welfare State, Michael Lipsky and Steven R. SMith, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 488)
  - Social Services: Federal Legislation vs. State Implementation, Bill Beaton, Tracy Feild, and Rhona Millar, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 489)
  - Regulations Implementing Title XX of the Social Security Act, Washington Bulletin, Jules H. Berman, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 490)
  - Private of Public: A Model of Ambiguities, Social Services Review, Eleanor L. Brilliant, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 491)
  - Social Reform Frustrated by Bureaucratic Routine: The XX in Massachusetts, Public Policy, Robert F. Cole, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 492)
  - Developments in Human Services, Volume 1: The Planning and Administration of Human Services: Resources and their Management, Harold W. Demone, Jr. and Dwight Harshbarger, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 493)
  - Purchase of Service: Forging Public-Private Partnership in the Human Services, Urban and Social Change, Margaret Gibelman and Harold Demone, Jr., 1983 (Box 57, Folder 494)
  - A "Fair Share" for the Aged: Title XX Allocation Patterns, 1976-1980, Neil Gilbert and Harry Specht, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 495)
  - Social Services to the Elderly under the Title XX: National Trends, 1976-1980, Neil Gilbert and Harry Specht, undated (Box 58, Folder 496)
  - The Burgeoning Social Service Payload, Neil Gilbert, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 497)
  - Capitalism and the Welfare State: Dilemmas of Social Benevolence, Neil Gilbert, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 498)
  - The Transformation of Social Services, Neil Gilbert, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 499)
  - The Wolf Comes Knocking at Nonprofit Doors, Business Week, K.H. Hammonds, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 500)
  - How Nonprofits Grow: A Model, Estelle James, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 501)
  - Public Social Services: The Next Phase - Policy and Delivery Strategies, Alfred J. Kahn, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 502)
  - Was Paul Biddle Too Tough on Stanford?, Marcia Barinaga, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 503)
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB) Circular A-21 and Revisions, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 504)
  - Government Funding of Scientific Instrumentation: A Review of U.S. Policy Debates since World War II, Jeffrey K. Stine and Gregory A. Good, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 505)
  - Indirect Costs/Allowable Costs, OMB Revises A-21, Adopts 26% Cap of Admin Costs of Research, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 506)
  - Indirect Costs/OMB Revisions to Circular A-21 "Cost Principles for Education Institutions", 1991 (Box 58, Folder 507)
  - Universities Discover that Simplicity Has Its Price, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 508)
  - GAO Faults University Accounting, OMB Guidance and Oversight, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 509)
  - Indirect Costs, OMB Delays Date for Admin Cost Cap, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 510)
  - Indirect Costs/OMB to Revise A-21 to Halt Universal Abuse of Indirect Costs, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 511)
  - Reimbursement Needs Change GAO Finds, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 512)